(
"ai_sub_version": "3.4.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-25T06:19:46.241852",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Ah ah ah ah ah
Hey! Every time, I'm so proud of you
Ah Touch my heart! & touch me please!
もっと近づいてほしい
I want you to come closer to me
どんなことも話してほしいのよ
I want you to tell me everything
Ah Touch my heart! & touch me please!
出来そうもないくらいなこと
Even things that seem impossible...
おねだりしてくれていいよ
It's okay to ask me for them
ずっと憧れてた人と再会した
I reunited with the one I've always longed for
運命感じなきゃ嘘だよ
It'd be a lie if I didn't feel it's destiny
嘘だよ
Just kidding!
Now! Touch my heart
100年たって地球が変わっても
Even if 100 years pass and the Earth changes
気持ちは変わらないわ 愛の園
My feelings won't change in this garden of love
Now! Touch my heart
なんだって 私が邪魔ならば
Even if I'm in the way,
良い子の私は bye bye
the good girl in me will say bye-bye.
Hey! Every time I'm so proud of you
Touch my heart! & touch me please!
もっといじわるでいいよ
You can be meaner to me.
過去も未来もあなたの自由でしょ！
The past and future are up to you, right?
Touch my heart! & touch me please!
夢は夢と言うの？
Do you say a dream is just a dream?
あなたの夢を知りたい
I want to know your dream.
ずっと忘れない夜が続いているわ
An unforgettable night continues.
運命抱きしめて眠るわ
I'll embrace fate and sleep.
Now! Touch my heart 千年経って宇宙で暮らしても
Now! Touch my heart! Even if a thousand years pass and we live in space,
私は変わらないわ 愛の園
I won't change in the Garden of Love.
Now! Touch my heart 明日になって私が邪魔ならば
Now! Touch my heart! If tomorrow comes and I'm in the way,
良い子の私は bye bye
the good girl in me will say bye-bye.
Let's go! One, two, one, two, one!
Now! Touch my heart 千年経って宇宙で暮らしても
Now! Touch my heart! Even if a thousand years pass and we live in space,
私は変わらないわ 愛の園
I won't change in the Garden of Love.
Now! Touch my heart 明日になって私が邪魔ならば
Now! Touch my heart! If tomorrow comes and I'm in the way,
良い子の私は bye bye
the good girl in me will say bye-bye.
Hey! Every time I'm so proud of you
Kikiriki~!
Hi, I'm Takanashi Kiara from hololive English -Myth-!
And welcome to my 3rd 3D Birthday Live today!
The first song was an iconic...
relatively old song from Morning Musume called "Ai no Sono"!
Yeah, did you like it?
There were like some funny moves. It's just like, what am I?
Yeah! So, as you can see, today once again I'm doing a Hello! Project Cover Song Birthday Festival!
It's my second time doing a Hello! Project cover song-themed live!
Did you watch the last one? I hope you did!
And back then, there were a bunch of songs that I felt like, "Ah, I still wanna do those so badly!"
And that's why we're here today!
And yeah, so a lot of Hello! Project songs to look forward to!
Also, ta-da! Hashtag #KiaraBday2026,
please use it!
Make me famous!
Take some screenshots,
some clips!
Tell the internet about this, what's happening here!
Also, let's talk a little bit about the background.
What is this, you might wonder?
If you have watched a lot of Hello! Project music videos in your life, you might actually recognize this because it's from...
a Morning Musume song, like inspired by the music video!
Maybe an upcoming song, maybe after this!
So we will have corners today!
We're starting right now with the Morning Musume corner!
And then we'll have other corners, too, that are all dedicated to my favorite Hello! Project groups!
And for each corner, there will be a representative backdrop,
like this one.
So please pay attention to the different variations of the stages today.
And now I'm kind of sad because I danced alone. I want some friends to come and help me perform!
So shall we begin and continue with the next song?
Yes, yes! Bring in the ladies!
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!
笑った顔をして返事した
I replied with a smile on my face,
あなたがウソをつく合図だね
that's your signal that you're lying to me.
二年目の記念を前にして
With our second anniversary coming up,
わたしが振られちゃって終わるのね
it's going to end with me getting dumped.
「また一人ぼっち」
"All alone again,"
自分に言い聞かす私
I tell myself.
気が付かないフリをしていつまでも
Pretending not to notice forever,
抱きしめられていようかな
maybe I'll just let you hold me.
ああ あなたが優しいのわかってる
Ah, I know you're gentle,
けどその分つらすぎるの
but that makes it hurt all the more.
お祈りをしたけれど
Even though I prayed,
心は遠く離れてゆく
our hearts keep drifting far apart.
ああ 私からお別れ告げようと
Ah, I thought I'd break up with you first,
そう思ったけど出来ない
that's what I thought, but I can't.
会話の中で何度も
So many times during our conversation,
タイミング見てたけど
I was looking for the right timing, but...
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry
かも
Maybe...
どうしてそんなに無理するの
Why do you push yourself so hard?
嫌ならお別れを言ってよね
If you don't like it, just say goodbye.
わざとわがままをしてみたけれど
I deliberately acted selfishly,
優しく笑顔で答える人
but you're someone who answers with a gentle smile.
「これでいいの？」
"Is this okay?"
自問自答する私
Asking myself...
最後だって言う前に抱きしめて
Hold me before you say it's over,
冷たくていいから
even if it feels cold.
そのあなたの優しさが罪なのよ
That kindness of yours is a sin.
ほら決心が鈍くなる
See, my resolve is weakening.
出会った頃みたいに
Just like when we first met,
毎日確かめ合いたい
I want us to confirm our feelings every day.
ああ もう少しこのまま居たいけど
Ah, I want to stay like this a little longer,
そう あなたと居たいけれど
yes, I want to be with you, but...
最後の夜が来たら
When the final night comes,
強気な振りしながら
while pretending to be strong...
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry
かも
Maybe...
そのあなたの優しさが罪なのよ
That kindness of yours is a sin.
ほら決心が鈍くなる
See, my resolve is weakening.
出会った頃みたいに
Just like when we first met,
毎日確かめ合いたい
I want us to confirm our feelings every day.
ああ もう少しこのまま居たいけど
Ah, I want to stay like this a little longer,
そう あなたと居たいけれど
yes, I want to be with you, but...
最後の夜が来たら
When the final night comes,
強気な振りしながら
while pretending to be strong...
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry
かも
Maybe...
早く
Hurry...
会いたいの...
I want to see you...
ねぇ 早く
Hey, hurry...
あなたに会いたい
I want to see you...
ヘイアー ホエイオエイ
Heya hoeyaoe
ヘイアー ホエイオー
Heya hoeyao
先に向かってる ROAD
Heading toward the road ahead
止まらない ミュージック
Music that won't stop
恋人からの花束
A bouquet from a lover
真夜中届くメール
An email arriving at midnight
女の子なら 誰でも思う
Any girl would dream of a...
HAPPY END STORY
やさしくされりゃ 嬉しいけど
It's nice to be treated gently, but
限りなく求めちゃう
I end up demanding endlessly
色っぽい キューピッド
Sexy Cupid
じれったい キスもっと
Tantalizing, kiss me more
熱い鼓動の SEXY ISLAND
Sexy Island of hot heartbeats
笑ってる星も
Both the smiling stars
気取ってる午後も
and the preening afternoon
この愛を見届けてほしい
I want you to watch over this love
ほしい
I want it...
ヘイアー ホエイオエイ
Heya hoeyaoe
ヘイアー ホエイオー
Heya hoeyao
運命が輝いて ジェラシー
Fate shines with jealousy
ひとりごとの週末
A weekend of talking to myself
あなたといたならうれしい
I'd be happy if I were with you
不思議な匂い SWEETIE
A mysterious scent, sweetie
寂しい夜と 楽しい時間
Lonely nights and fun times
HAPPY END STORY
もう一度言うわ 大好きです
I'll say it once more: I love you
抱きしめて 離さないで
Hold me close and don't let go
色っぽい ビスケット
Sexy biscuit
じれったい ミスショット
Tantalizing, miss shot
ずっと続くの SEXY ISLAND
Sexy Island that continues forever
愛して 急接近
Love me, rapid approach
未来に 大接近
A giant leap toward the future
どこまでも抱きしめてほしい
I want you to hold me everywhere
ほしい
I want it...
色っぽい キューピッド
Sexy Cupid
じれったい キスもっと
Tantalizing, kiss me more
熱い鼓動の SEXY ISLAND
Sexy Island of hot heartbeats
笑ってる星も
Both the smiling stars
気取ってる午後も
and the preening afternoon
この愛を見届けてほしい
I want you to watch over this love
ほしい
I want it...
色っぽい ビスケット
Sexy biscuit
じれったい ミスショット
Tantalizing, miss shot
ずっと続くの SEXY ISLAND
Sexy Island that continues forever
愛して 急接近
Love me, rapid approach
未来に 大接近
A giant leap toward the future
どこまでも抱きしめてほしい
I want you to hold me everywhere
ほしい
I want it...
ヘイアー ホエイオエイ
Heya hoeyaoe
ヘイアー ホエイオー
Heya hoeyao
ヘイアー ホエイオエイ
Heya hoeyaoe
ヘイアー ホエイオー
Heya hoeyao
°C-ute
Isaki Riona
Koganei Niko
Mizumiya Su
Rindo Chihaya
Kikirara Vivi
渋谷を歩く
I walk around Shibuya
一人で歩く
I walk alone
人ごみの中
In the middle of the crowd
いつ気付いたの あの愛しさ 探す
When did you realize it? Searching for that affection...
手をつないでいい？ その思いから
"May I hold your hand?" From that thought...
うんと早く 触れてみたいだけなの
I just want to touch you as soon as possible.
そんな人を この私を
Such a person... someone like me...
どうか離さないでね
Please don't ever let go.
恋する思いが マイダーリン
My feelings of love, My Darling,
大きく膨らむ I love you
are swelling up so big, I love you.
考えすぎたら マイダーリン
When I overthink things, My Darling,
空回りしたの
I just end up spinning my wheels.
まだまだ私は マイダーリン
I'm still so inexperienced, My Darling,
あなたが怖いわ I love you
I'm almost scared of loving you so much, I love you.
きっといつの日か マイダーリン
I feel like someday, My Darling,
照れ笑っちゃいそうで
we'll look back and laugh shyly about this.
あなたを見つけ
Finding you,
涙勝って出ちゃった
tears fell all on their own.
少し前から
I asked, "Did you notice me...
私に気づいてたの？って
...a little while ago?"
少しズルいよ
That's a bit unfair,
だけど言えない
but I can't say it out loud,
最初のきっかけは私だし
since I was the one who started it all.
そうよ うつむいてたら
That's right, when I was looking down,
手を握ってくれたわ
you took my hand in yours.
大人になっても マイダーリン
Even when we grow up, My Darling,
もっとその先も I love you
and even far beyond that, I love you.
腰が曲がっても マイダーリン
Even when our backs bend with age, My Darling,
手をつなぐ時には
whenever we hold hands,
ドキドキするでしょう マイダーリン
our hearts will still flutter, won't they, My Darling?
恥ずかしいでしょう I love you
It might feel embarrassing, I love you.
それでも私を マイダーリン
Even so, My Darling,
優しく包んでね
please wrap me in your gentle embrace.
大人になっても マイダーリン
Even when we grow up, My Darling,
もっとその先も I love you
and even far beyond that, I love you.
腰が曲がっても マイダーリン
Even when our backs bend with age, My Darling,
手をつなぐ時には
whenever we hold hands,
ドキドキするでしょう マイダーリン
our hearts will still flutter, won't they, My Darling?
恥ずかしいでしょう I love you
It might feel embarrassing, I love you.
それでも私を マイダーリン
Even so, My Darling,
優しく包んでね
please wrap me in your gentle embrace.
涙の色
[Title: The Color of Tears]
強情 あなたは強情
Stubborn, you're so stubborn.
分からず屋のままね
You're still as clueless as ever.
もう付き合いきれない
I can't deal with you anymore.
サヨナラ愛し人
Goodbye, my beloved.
友情 「友達」なんて
Friendship? There's no way...
戻れるわけないでしょ
...we can ever go back to being "friends."
この先もわがままに
You just intend to keep pushing me around...
振り回すつもり
...with your selfishness.
浮気なら それなりに
If it was just an affair, I might have...
許すつもりだった
...forgiven you in my own way.
プライドを 傷つけた
But I can't forgive that day...
あの日は許せない
...when you hurt my pride.
涙 止まらぬ涙
Tears, tears that won't stop falling.
これでスキッとするわ
This will clear my mind and refresh me.
あなたを信じてた
That day I believed in you...
あの日は...
...was such a waste...
Ah...
それでも愛してた
Even so, I loved you
あなたとのサヨナラ
Goodbye to you
動揺 心の隙間
Agitation, a gap in my heart
風邪を引きそうだケド
It feels like I'm catching a cold
それならすぐ治るし...
But if so, it'll heal quickly...
サヨナラ愛し人
Goodbye, my love
薄情 どう言われても
Cold-hearted, no matter what you say
寄りを戻さないから
I won't get back together with you
もう電話は出ないわ
I won't answer the phone anymore
どんなに寂しくても
No matter how lonely I get
いつもより早いケド
It's earlier than usual, but
ベッドに入るわ
I'm going to bed
懐かしい記憶との
It's time to fight
戦いの時間
with nostalgic memories
涙 思い出 涙 悲しくなんか無いよ
Tears, memories, tears, I'm not sad at all
私 も強情ね 今頃そう思うわ
I'm stubborn too, I realize that now
あんなに愛してた あなたとのサヨナラ
Goodbye to you, whom I loved so much
涙 止まらぬ涙 これでスキッとするわ
Tears, unstoppable tears, this will clear my head
あなたを信じてた あの日がもったいない
Believing in you back then was such a waste
涙 思い出 涙 悲しくなんか無いよ
Tears, memories, tears, I'm not sad at all
私 も強情ね 今頃そう思うわ
I'm stubborn too, I realize that now
あんなに愛してた あなたとのサヨナラ
Goodbye to you, whom I loved so much
Welcome, welcome!
That was FOREVER LOVE and 涙の色 with FLOW GLOW!
That was "FOREVER LOVE" and "Namida no Iro" with FLOW GLOW!
なんか FLOW GLOW のメンバーになった気分！
It's like I'm a member of FLOW GLOW!
7人目のメンバー！
Another member!
いや、めっちゃ嬉しいです！こんなに大人数で、うん、踊れて！
I'm so happy we could dance with so many people!
まずは、自己紹介をみんなに、英語でやってもらおうかな！
First of all, I'd like everyone to introduce themselves in English!
えー！英語！？やばい、できるかな？
English? Oh no, can I do it?
インターナショナル！
International!
がんばれ！
Good luck!
順番はお任せしますけど！
I'll leave the order up to you!
じゃあ、いつもの順番で！
Then let's go in the usual order!
Hello, everyone! My name is Riona! I'm FLOW GLOW leader! Proper... yeah!
Hello, everyone! My name is Riona! I'm FLOW GLOW's leader! Proper... Yeah!
パーフェクト！
Perfect!
次は！
Next!
Niko-tan count key! My name is Koganei Niko! FLOW GLOW... comedian modoki! Yeah!
Niko-tan, count key! My name is Koganei Niko! FLOW GLOW's... comedian modoki! Yeah!
モドキ？英語がちょっと足りないけど！
Modoki? Her English was a bit lacking though!
はい！ちひわ！Big car, rhythm... Yes!
Yes! Chishiwa... Big car, rhythm... Yes!
あれ？PR担当...
Wait, PR manager...
ちーちゃん、日本語の「大き」は英語で「small」！
Chishi-chan, the "oki" in Japanese is "small" in English!
No! No!
Yes, small! Classmate, thank you!
バカだと思っていただろ！さすが Kiara先輩！
I thought she was stupid! As expected of Kiara-senpai!
Hi! FLOW GLOW DJ and driver, Rindo Chihaya!
めちゃめちゃギャルやってた！
You guys were total gals!
おー！すごーい！
Woah! Amazing!
Big感謝！Big感謝！
Big thanks! Big thanks!
ピンク・ビーフ！
Pink Beef!
はい、せーの、うー、V！
Okay, one, two, three... V!
うー、I'm スゲヨ キキララ ViViっと！
I'm Sugeyo Kikilara Vivi-tte!
スゲヨがそんな公式じゃないかもしれない...
"Sugeyo" might not actually be official...
Well, when I chose to do these songs, I really wanted to bring in FLOW GLOW because I know they're all really good at dancing and performing.
みんなパフォーマンス上手いから、絶対FLOW GLOW誘おうと思って、完成度高いと思って。
Everyone's so good at performing, so I definitely wanted to invite FLOW GLOW, knowing the quality would be high.
でも、なんか困ったこととか、難しかった振りとか何かありましたか？
But was there anything you struggled with or any difficult choreo?
全部！全部難しかった！
All of it! All of it was hard!
え、でもカッコよかった！揃ったの見て「めっちゃカッコいい！」ってなりました！
But you all looked so cool! Seeing everyone in sync made me go, "That's super cool!"
私も！みんなでどんどん出来上がって、完成度が高くなっていくうちに...
Me too! As we all put it together and the quality got higher and higher...
もう幸せすぎて！「めっちゃカッコいい！」って言ってくれて嬉しかった！
I was just so happy! I was so glad when you told us, "That's super cool!"
カノンで結構交互の振りとか、あんまなかったから...
We haven't done many alternating or canon moves like that before...
キアラ先輩に呼ばれてそれができて嬉しかったです！
So I was really happy that Kiara-senpai invited us and we got to do it!
そうだね、順番で回るとか結構多くて...
Yeah, there were quite a lot of moves where we turned in sequence...
大変でした。すみません、難しい振付で...
It was tough. Sorry for giving you such difficult choreo...
皆さんのコーナーはFLOW GLOWのコーナーであって...
That corner was FLOW GLOW's corner...
FLOW GLOWっていうグループは、ダンスがマジでいつも難しい...
And as a group, FLOW GLOW always has seriously difficult dances...
実力派！
You're so talented!
ごめんね！でもみんなよくできてた！めっちゃ楽しかった！
Sorry about that! But you all did so well! It was super fun!
FLOW GLOWといえば、I want to know everybody's favorite Hello! Project song! ハロプロの好きな曲、知りたいけど...
Speaking of FLOW GLOW, I want to know everybody's favorite Hello! Project song! I want to know your favorite Hello! Project songs...
じゃあ、まずすーちゃんありますか？
First off, Su-chan, do you have one?
『あーオレ！あーオレ！』が好き！
I love "Ah-Ore! Ah-Ore!"!
おー！最近の曲ですね！いいですね！
Oh! That's a recent song! Nice!
あとニコちゃんは？
How about Niko-chan?
『ばかやろう！女、自分、盛大に抱いてやれ！』が好きです！
I love "Bakayarou! Onna, Jibun, Seidai ni Daite Yare!"!
いいよねー！すごくカッコいい！わかるー！
That's a great one! So cool! I totally get it!
結構オタクと聞いて...
I heard you're quite an otaku...
私の好きな曲はモーニング娘。'14さんの『時空を超え 宇宙を超え』！
My favorite song is Morning Musume '14's "Toki wo Koe Sora wo Koe"!
あー！好き！名曲！オタクは名曲で...
Ah! I love that! A total masterpiece! Real otaku go for the classics...
『時空を超え〜 宇宙を超え〜』って...
"Toki wo koe~ Sora wo koe~"...
カッコいい！知ってるだけでカッコいい！
So cool! Just knowing that one makes you cool!
スマイレージさんは『天真爛漫』とか『天の邪鬼』...
For S/mileage, songs like "Tenshinranman" or "Amanojaku"...
『天の邪鬼』は去年やってたんですよ！私『天の邪鬼』大好きです！
We performed "Amanojaku" last year! I absolutely love "Amanojaku"!
なるほど！詳しそうですね！
I see! You really know your stuff!
ルチちゃんはどの曲が...？
Lico-chan, which song do you like?
私は『ソラシド〜ねえねえ〜』が、初めて聴いた時に「めっちゃ素敵な曲だな」と思って...
For me, when I first heard "Sorashido ~Nee Nee~", I thought, "What a wonderful song..."
Buono!ですね！みんな大好きなBuono!ですね！わかる！
That's Buono!, right? Everyone loves Buono!! I get it!
と、ビビは？
And how about Vivi?
ビビは『チュッ！チュッ！チュッ！夏パ〜ティ』！キアラ先輩に注入したいわ！
For me, it's "Chu! Chu! Chu! Natsu Party"! I want to inject it into Kiara-senpai!
チュッ！チュッ！チュッ！チュッ！チュッ！やめてー！
Chu! Chu! Chu! Chu! Chu! Stop it~!
先輩、騙されないでください！
Senpai, don't be fooled!
可愛い！でも、いろんな曲名を聞くだけで...
How cute! But just hearing all these song titles...
ハロプロカバーソングライブ、何度も何度もやりたいですけど...
I want to do this Hello! Project cover song live over and over again...
とりあえずは、まだまだあります！FLOW GLOWの次に他のパートもありますので...
For now, there's still plenty more! After FLOW GLOW, we have other parts coming up...
次のパートに行きましょう！FLOW GLOWのみんな、ありがとう！
Let me move on to the next part! Thank you, everyone in FLOW GLOW!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
Let's go to the next corner!
イエーイ！
Yay!
S/mileage
犬神ころね
[Inugami Korone]
兎田ぺこら
[Usada Pekora]
ワトソン・エイミリア
[Watson Amelia]
今だかつてないような
Like nothing ever before,
キラキラした毎日
every day is sparkling.
ぶっちゃけ有頂天な日々送ってる
To be honest, I'm spending ecstatic days!
恋をしたら勉強が
Once in love, studying...
手につかない今
...I can't focus on it right now.
恋のせいにして...ない！
I'm blaming it on love... wait, no!
今日はデート 彼と10時に待ち合わせてるの
Today is a date, I'm meeting him at 10 o'clock!
Wow wow
ちょっと香りを少し変えたこと気づくかしら君は
I wonder if you'll notice that I changed my scent a little.
Wow wow
ドクターストップが掛かるほど “恋落ち”してるわ
I'm falling in love to the point of a doctor's stop.
大好きが止まらない
I can't stop loving you!
Oh love me, love me, love me, love me, love me do!
Wow wow
カルチャーショックを起こすほど 時代を変えるわ
It'll change the era to the point of causing culture shock!
スポットライトを浴びる二人 口づけをしましょう！
The two of us bathed in spotlights, let's kiss!
I love you!
女の子には秘密の 恋のボタンがあるのよ
Girls have a secret love button, you know.
今年の夏は負けない
I won't lose this summer.
去年みたいに弱くない
I'm not weak like last year.
イヤイヤイヤン 夏真ん中 胸が騒ぐわ
No, no, no! In the middle of summer, my heart races.
イヤイヤイヤン
No, no, no!
実際 恋するだけなら 誰でも出来る
Honestly, anyone can just fall in love.
勇気をもっと出さなきゃ
I have to show more courage.
実際 恋愛するのって大変
Actually being in a relationship is tough.
見逃せない
I can't let this chance pass by.
夏祭り 手をつなぎ
Holding hands at the summer festival,
花火を見上げて
looking up at the fireworks...
きれいだと 私みて
"It's beautiful," you say, looking at me,
君が言う
that's what you'd say.
浴衣着て 金魚すくい 君が魅力的で
Wearing yukatas, scooping goldfish, you're so attractive...
なんて恋 夢見てる フィフティーン
What a love I'm dreaming of, at fifteen.
一人きり イヤホンで
All alone, with earphones on,
音楽聴いている
listening to music...
意味もなく 涙とか
Tears start falling
出てきちゃう
for no reason at all.
寂しいよ 寂しいよ
I'm lonely, I'm so lonely.
なぜか寂しいよ
For some reason, I feel so lonely.
すごい恋 夢見てる
Dreaming of an amazing love...
フィフティーン
...at fifteen.
サマーラブ
Summer love.
どういうロジックが
What kind of logic is that?
あるんでしょうか
Do you even have?
ねぇ君は
Hey, what about you?
おどおどしてっちゃ
If you're timid,
呑み込まれるよ
you'll be swallowed up
都会では
in the big city.
愛だ恋だと言ってるつもりなら
If you intend to talk about love and romance,
それなりに
do it properly.
男らしくて
Be manly,
自信ありげで
look confident,
爽やかに
and stay refreshing.
私だってそれなりに甘えたいと思う
I want to be spoiled to some extent too,
だけど甘い顔は出来ない立場なの
but I'm in no position to show a soft face.
胸元の開いた服を着た私の
In my low-cut outfit,
サインに気づいて
notice my signal...
ねぇ
Hey!
愛してよ
Love me!
誰にも負けず
More than anyone else,
愛して 愛して 愛しすぎて
love me, love me, love me too much!
安心感
Peace of mind,
優越感
a sense of superiority,
それが欲しいの
that's what I want.
抱きしめて
Hold me close!
生まれたままの
Just as I was born,
裸の 裸の 裸のKISS
a naked, naked, naked KISS.
この愛が
If I know
本物と
this love is real,
分かればいいの
that's all that matters.
この愛が
So I know
本物と
this love is real,
分かるように KISSして
kiss me!
愛してよ
Love me!
もう一巡フォロー
Follow me for one more round!
愛して 愛して 愛しすぎて
Love me, love me, love me too much!
少し位
Being a little
強引で
forceful
ちょうどいいのよ
is just right.
抱きしめて
Hold me close!
生まれたままの
Just as I was born,
裸の 裸の 裸のKISS
a naked, naked, naked KISS.
この愛が
If I know
本物と
this love is real,
分かればいいの
that's all that matters.
この愛が
So I know
本物と
this love is real,
分かるように KISSして
kiss me!
盛れ！ミ・アモーレ
Glam up, Mi Amore!
盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！
Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up!
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, Mi Amore,
一番の私を見て
look at the best version of me!
ありのままなんて 愛したくはない
I don't want to love someone "just as they are."
火花みたいな 今を
Right now, like a spark...
盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！
Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up!
あなたの瞳はフィルター
Your eyes are a filter.
燃えてゆく恋は切ない
A burning love is painful.
思い出なら 綺麗なまま 笑っていられるの？
If it's just a memory, can I keep smiling while staying beautiful?
泣いてなんかないよ
I'm not crying or anything,
素顔になんて戻せなくて あなたにこそ 羽ひろげ
I can't go back to being unglamorous, so to you I spread my wings.
ドタバタの角度で 悪魔でも味付ける
Styling myself from chaotic angles, giving even a devil flavor,
美しさのせいにして
blaming it all on beauty.
油断できないわ シャッターチャンス
I can't let my guard down, it's a photo op!
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, Mi Amore,
私を好きでいさせて
let me stay in love with myself!
ありのままなんて 慰めたくない
I don't want to comfort myself with "just as I am."
現実以上 理想の
Beyond reality, the ideal...
盛れ！ミ・アモーレ
Glam up, Mi Amore!
一番の私を見て
Look at the best version of me!
ありのままなんて 愛したくはない
I don't want to love someone "just as they are."
火花みたいな 今を
Right now, like a spark...
盛れ！
Glam up!
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, Mi Amore,
あなたを好きでいさせて
let me stay in love with you!
愛してよかったと 威張れるから
So I can boast that I'm glad I loved you,
綺麗にしないわ だって
I won't play nice, because...
盛れ！ミ・アモーレ
Glam up, Mi Amore!
私のもとを去るため
So that you leave my side,
虚しい空で 気持ちが悪い
under a hollow sky, it feels disgusting.
めちゃくちゃにして 離そう
Mess it all up and let go!
盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！ 盛れ！
Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up!
ライ ライ ライ...
Lai, lai, lai...
M-O-R-E M-O-R-E
オレ！
Olé!
今夜は会えそうにない　ヤイヤイ
Looks like we won't be able to meet tonight, yay-yay
不思議と寂しい　ヤイヤイヤイヤイ
Strangely enough, I feel so lonely, yay-yay-yay-yay
背伸びをしてるわけじゃないのに胸が痛い
It's not like I'm trying to act grown-up, but my heart hurts
仲間が集まってガキ扱い
When my friends hang out, they treat me like a kid
今すぐ大人になりたい　ヤイ
I want to grow up right now, yay
こんなに苦しいのが初恋ですか？
Is first love always this painful?
アーケード
The shopping arcade...
走り抜け
Running through it,
信号が青になる
the traffic light turns green.
あの人が
That special someone...
この時間
around this time,
ココを通る
passes right through here.
ほら
Look,
春紅のスカーレット
the spring crimson scarlet.
我慢なんて出来ない
I just can't hold back anymore.
胸さわぎスカーレット
A scarlet premonition...
恋の色が　か・お・る
The color of love is in the air.
Yes, my love
週末はみんなワイワイワイ
On the weekend, everyone's having fun, wai-wai
なぜなのあなたイナイワイワイワイ
Why aren't you here with us? Wai-wai-wai
こんな日はつまらない
Days like this are so boring,
そろそろ帰ろうかな...
maybe I should just go home...
噂じゃ彼女がデキタトカ
Rumor has it you got a girlfriend...
そんなのまったくキキタクナイ
I don't want to hear anything like that!
張り裂けそうなくらい頭がナナメ
My head feels like it's going crazy and about to burst!
雨が降る
Rain falls down,
週末は少し街も静か
on weekends, the town gets a little quieter.
このままじゃ眠れない
If things stay like this, I won't be able to sleep.
せつなすぎる
It hurts far too much.
Ah 春紅のスカーレット
Ah, the spring crimson scarlet.
そっと近づきたい
I want to gently get closer to you.
胸さわぎスカーレット
A scarlet premonition...
恋の虹が　ひ・か・る
The rainbow of love is shining bright.
Yes, my love
ほら
Look,
春紅のスカーレット
the spring crimson scarlet.
我慢なんて出来ない
I just can't hold back anymore.
胸さわぎスカーレット
A scarlet premonition...
恋の色が　か・お・る
The color of love is in the air.
Yes, my love
Ah 春紅のスカーレット
Ah, the spring crimson scarlet.
そっと近づきたい
I want to gently get closer to you.
胸さわぎスカーレット
A scarlet premonition...
恋の虹が　ひ・か・る
The rainbow of love is shining bright.
Yes, my love
Here we go!
Oh my god!
Welcome back!
Kiara, happy birthday!
Thank you! It's not just my birthday, but it's another celebration...
...because this is the first time that we're together as a duo!
What an occasion!
How we have come to this occasion, you will never know.
But please introduce yourself.
What's up! I am Chaos, the End of Events...
...a still world trapped in a cage of ice, your best friend...
...Baelz Hakos from hololive English -Promise-!
Witness...
...me!
Such a good introduction!
Woah, I wish I had such an introduction!
Well, welcome, welcome, welcome! How did you like the song?
It was so hard!
Yeah, really?
I don't do idol dances. This...
This is so hard!
Ah, yes, yeah.
That happens often in Hello! Project, but...
I don't understand!
But this... I remember in the dance lesson...
...you told me about the different genres...
...of dance that appear in this.
That was quite a surprise.
Yeah, a lot of House.
This is quite House-y.
This is House?
House.
Okay.
And then there's also Locking.
Ah, this... You said that's Rock?
This is Locking.
Ah, Locking.
Oh, you meant Locking, not Rocking!
No, Locking!
Oh, I thought that was some Rock dance style. Okay.
No, Locking.
Makes sense now.
Yeah!
That was so hard!
You did so well!
I was so surprised.
I was like, "What kind of idol dance has House and Locking in the same dance?" That's crazy!
They were trying all kinds of things back then, but...
...yeah, that's from my favorite idol group BEYOOOOONDS...
...and it's like a pretty old song at this point.
But it has this one part in the choreography...
...that I thought would be perfect for like a duo.
So I thought, "I want to do it with you together!"
Is this part...
Sorry!
That was fun!
I really wanted to do it. Thank you!
Okay. Um, I have also prepared a little game for us.
A game!
A game of cameras!
There are so many cameras, and I would like to make use of it.
We'll play a game where you have to find the camera.
Is this the first camera that we're looking for standardly so far?
Maybe it's like here? Uh... uh, yeah!
Hi!
I see, I see, I see.
Yeah! Okay, Bae, you find the next one.
Where is that?
Is it there? Or is it the opposite?
I want to find it first!
No, where is it?
あれ？あれ？あれ？あれ？
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Well, if we continue running around, surely we will find it eventually...
Ah!
Wait, hold on. Oh...
Right there!
Wait, wait, wait, no.
I see it right there!
Ah, hello!
Hi!
That one's really difficult!
That was fun.
Next, where is it?
Where do they find these cameras?
I see you!
When is this angle ever being used?
Hi!
こんにちは！
Hello!
One more! One more! One more!
One more.
あれ？あれ？ Under the disco ball?
Huh? Huh? Under the disco ball?
Wait, it's under the shadow.
Wait, the disco ball should be like...
Oh, oh, oh!
No, it's like... No! No!
It's not there!
No!
It's like...
Ah!
Am I looking at it?
Ah! Yeah!
Ah!
Yeah! Okay, okay, okay.
Wait, what? One last, though? Last one?
Is that the last one?
Well, this one's easy because...
That's not a challenge!
Hi!
Yeah!
Okay, okay, okay! That was fun!
Ah. Well, well, well. Well...
This is not the end, though!
No, no, no. What are you doing next?
First of all, the BEYOOOOONDS / CHICA#TETSU corner will continue.
One more song, because I love them so much.
Oh!
And for the next one...
...I have four guests!
Four?!
And they are none other than Justice!
Because last year...
...for the Easter Hello! Project Cover Song Live...
...I also had them over, but they were in 2D, like in paper form.
Oh!
Right?
So I thought, well this year, I got them all in 3D!
3D! Justice!
Yeah, and they will be wearing like a little bit of a costume...
Oh, a cosplay?
Something like that. That matches the music video.
So pay attention to what's different.
And with that, I guess...
...have fun with the rest of the show!
And the next song, which is...
せーの！『せいしゅんバスガイド』！
Ready, go! "Seishun Bus Guide"!
今日でサヨナラ
Today is goodbye,
胸が苦しい
my chest hurts.
手紙書いていいんだろう？
Should I write a letter?
青春バスガイド
Youth bus guide,
君はまぶしい
you are so dazzling.
記念に写真とっていいかい？
Can I take a picture to remember this?
ひとめぼれなんだ
It was love at first sight,
僕がはじけた
I burst open.
とまらない感覚
This unstoppable feeling,
これが恋だろう？
is this love?
君とすれ違う
As I pass by you,
いい匂いがした
you smelled so nice.
みんなに優しくするなよ
Don't be so kind to everyone.
ひとりじめしたいんだ
I want you all to myself.
その声 その笑顔 全部
That voice, that smile, all of it.
目線が合う度 しびれるよ
Every time our eyes meet, I get thrills.
ひとりじめしたいんだ
I want you all to myself!
だけどサヨナラ
But it's goodbye,
胸が苦しい
my chest hurts.
もっと話していたい
I want to talk with you more.
青春バスガイド
Youth bus guide,
君はまぶしい
you are so dazzling.
マイクに生まれ変わりたい
I want to be reborn as a microphone.
あいつもライバル
She's a rival, too,
話しかけてる
talking to you.
沸き起こる感覚
This feeling welling up,
これがジェラシー
is this jealousy?
休憩時間に
During break time,
少し会話できた
we talked a little bit.
まつげがとても長いね
Your eyelashes are so long.
時間よ戻ってくれ
Time, please turn back,
最初の日に戻りたい
I want to go back to the first day.
君に伝えたいことばかり
There's so much I want to tell you.
時間よ戻ってくれ
Time, please turn back!
ひとりじめしたいんだ
I want you all to myself.
その声 その笑顔 全部
That voice, that smile, all of it.
目線が合う度 しびれるよ
Every time our eyes meet, I get thrills.
ひとりじめしたいんだ
I want you all to myself!
今日でサヨナラ
Today is goodbye,
胸が苦しい
my chest hurts.
手紙書いていいんだろう？
Should I write a letter?
青春バスガイド
Youth bus guide,
君はまぶしい
you are so dazzling.
記念に写真撮っていたいかい
Can I take a picture to remember this?
だけどサヨナラ
But it's goodbye,
胸が苦しい
my chest hurts.
もっと話していたい
I want to talk with you more.
青春バスガイド
Youth bus guide,
君はまぶしい
you are so dazzling.
もう一度君に会いたいよ
I want to see you once more!
スッペシャル ジェネレーション
[Title: Special Generation]
どうたら こうたら 言い訳してる
You keep making excuses about this and that.
イライラ くるなぁ
It's getting on my nerves!
あの子が良いなら
If you like her better,
そっち行けばいいじゃん
why don't you just go to her?
チャラチャラ チャラチャラ
Flashy and playful,
シルバー着けて フラフラしてる
wearing silver accessories, flirting around.
誰にあぴってるの？
Who are you trying to appeal to?
余所見なんて 許さないわよ
I won't forgive you for looking away!
好きと 好きと 好きと 好きと言いなさい
Say "I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you"!
そう この場で スッペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Yes, right here, Special Generation LOVE!
運命を信じたい
I want to believe in fate.
100万年過ぎたって
Even if a million years pass,
この愛は ゆ・る・ぎ・な・い
this love is u-n-s-h-a-k-a-b-l-e!
スッペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special Generation LOVE!
嫌いにもなれないわ
I can't even hate you.
地下鉄の中だって 過去よりも あ・い・し・て！
Even on the subway, love me more than ever!
昨日よりも
More than yesterday,
愛して
love me.
あったらあったで どこに行っても
Even if we do, no matter where we go,
だらだらしちゃう
we just end up slacking off.
私があと決めなきゃ
If I don't decide,
何も始まらない
nothing will ever begin.
押したり引いたり
Pushing and pulling,
器用にする事出来ない
I can't play games like that skillfully.
まっすぐ行くゆえ
Because I go straight ahead...
誰も彼も驚くような
In a way that surprises everyone,
熱い愛で私 抱きしめて
hold me tight with passionate love.
スッペシャル ジェネレ〜ション LOVE
Special Generation Love!
孤独なんて感じない
I don't feel lonely at all.
池袋過ぎたって
Even past Ikebukuro,
この愛は永遠
this love is eternal!
スッペシャル ジェネレ〜ション LOVE
Special Generation Love!
離れない 離さない
I won't leave, I won't let go.
昨日よりも 今よりも また明日も 愛して
More than yesterday, more than now, love me again tomorrow.
スッペシャル ジェネレ〜ション LOVE
Special Generation Love!
孤独なんて感じない
I don't feel lonely at all.
池袋過ぎたって
Even past Ikebukuro,
この愛は永遠
this love is eternal!
スッペシャル ジェネレ〜ション LOVE
Special Generation Love!
離れない 離さない
I won't leave, I won't let go.
昨日よりも 今よりも また明日も 愛して
More than yesterday, more than now, love me again tomorrow.
スッペシャル ジェネレ〜ション
Special Generation!
Thank you so much, everybody!
Thank you for coming, thank you for watching!
Bye bye!
Bye-bye!
One more!
Bye bye!
Bye-bye!
Announcement, announcement!
Takanashi Kiara Birthday Merchandise 2026!
Here is the banner.
First of all, the big item that is the main character is a dakimakura!
First of all, the big item, the main attraction, is a dakimakura!
I finally did it after so many years of doing merchandise.
I finally made one after so many years of doing merch!
I might be running out of ideas a little bit, so...
I did something that originally I never thought I would do!
I made something I originally thought I'd never do!
KFP, don't leave me hanging, leave me laying on the bed, yeah!
1つ目のアイテムはなんと！
The first item is...
一生やらないと思ってたんですけど、やっぱりここまで活動すると、もう出すしかなかった
I thought I'd never do it, but after all this time, I just had to make one!
抱き枕です！
A body pillow cover!
やばい！
Amazing!
Next, we have a really cute plushie set of my kitty-katties, Smoothie and Chonkers!
Next, we have a really cute plushie set of my kitties, Smoothie and Chonkers!
They're so cute and fluffy, and I can bring them everywhere now,
and you should too! You can hang them on your bag or keys.
2つ目のアイテムはそうですね、私の猫たちのぬいぐるみセットで、
The second item is a plushie set of my cats...
キーチェーンなどとして使えます！
which can be used as keychains and more!
どこにでも連れて行ってあげてください。
Please take them with you everywhere!
Next one is these badges, but they're a bit unusual...
Next up are these badges, but they're a bit unusual...
because this time they are square and made from fake leather, so they're a bit squishy.
Of course you can make an ita-bag with this, too!
Of course you can make an ita-bag with these, too!
今回のバッジはなんと、フェイクレザーでできてますし、
This time, the badges are made from fake leather...
あと四角だし、変わっておりますが、
and they're square, so they're a bit unusual, but...
もちろんこれでも痛バッグとかできたりしますよ！
of course you can make an ita-bag with them too!
Last item is the smartphone ring...
The last item is a smartphone ring...
modeled after KFP chickens!
Maybe this way, holding your phones won't be as hard with your wings!
Cute!
最後のアイテムはスマホリング！
The last item is a smartphone ring!
もちろんKFPモチーフです！
It's KFP themed, of course!
Besides that, there's also a voice pack!
I haven't been doing any voice packs these past months, so make sure to get this one. Rare!
その他には、久しぶりにボイスもあります！
Besides that, there's also a voice pack for the first time in a while!
最近あんまり参加してないので、ぜひこの機会にお願いします！
I haven't done many lately, so please take this opportunity to get it!
If you get the full set, then you receive a polaroid from me alongside it,
and if you're lucky to get the limited one, then it will be signed by my own hands.
もちろんいつも通りフルセットゲットすると... えーまチェキついてきます！
Of course, as usual, if you get the full set, it comes with a photocard!
限定版だとキアラのサイン入りですね！よろしくお願いします！
If you get the limited edition, it comes with Kiara's signature! Please check it out!
One more thing, before we end, I have a super awesome song cover coming up right after this!
It's a collaboration with some cuties that might be familiar to you...
iii! Yeah, iii!
この後は韓国のVTuberアイドルiiiとのコラボ歌ってみたプレミア公開しますので見てください！
Right after this, we'll premiere a song cover collaboration with Korean VTuber idol group iii, so please check it out!
We will try our best to raid you into it,
but if it does not work out, please make your way there on your own!
Besides that, thank you so much for celebrating my birthday today!
I worked so hard on this, and I'm really proud.
Please leave a comment and a like, and if you can, get the merchandise!
And in German, we say: Auf Wiedersehen!
最後に、今日はお誕生日お祝いに来てくれてありがとうございました！
Finally, thank you so much for coming to celebrate my birthday today!
本当に色々努力してきたのです！
I really worked so hard on all of this!
コメントといいね、そしてもし良かったらグッズもよろしくお願いいたします！
Please leave a comment and a like, and if you'd like, check out the merch as well!
ではでは、 Auf Wiedersehen!
Well then, Auf Wiedersehen!
See you in the song cover!
[画面上のメッセージ: "Did you have fun?! Thank you for watching ♡ Your love & support keeps me going!! I hope we can celebrate many more of my & your birthdays together! Danke schön. - Wawa"]
[On-screen note: "Did you have fun?! Thank you for watching ♡ Your love & support keeps me going!! I hope we can celebrate many more of my & your birthdays together! Danke schön. - Wawa"]